#### Contact

rncarolyn@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/carolyn-dixona9207780 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
ACLS
BLS
Nursing

# Carolyn Dixon

MSN, RN, FNP-BC, CEN, CCRN, TCRN

Staten Island, New York

## Summary

Experienced Professor Of Nursing with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Post Anesthesia Care, Nursing Education, Central Lines, and Medical-Surgical. Strong education professional with a MSN/FNP focused in Family nurse practitioner from Wagner College.

## Experience

Staten Island University Hospital 13 years 10 months

Emergency Department Educator September 2015 - Present (4 years 9 months)

RN Assistant Director of Nursing May 2010 - September 2015 (5 years 5 months)

Assistant Nurse Manager Emergency Department August 2006 - May 2011 (4 years 10 months)

New York University
Adjunct Nursing Professor
December 2013 - Present (6 years 6 months)
New York

#### SIUH

Rn

May 1995 - September 2009 (14 years 5 months)

intensive care unit

### Education

Wagner College

DNP, Nursing · (2018 - 2020)

Wagner College

MSN/FNP, Family nurse practitioner · (2011 - 2014)

Wagner College

BSN, MSN/FNP · (2008 - 2011)

Pasco-Hernando Community College

Associate of Arts and Sciences (AAS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse  $\cdot$  (1993 - 1995)